Guide to the Lesly Lempert Collection, 1987-1994.
Lempert, Lesly Collection
- Series I. Periodicals
  - (Press Release): Middle East Watch Finds Violations of the Laws of War by Both Sides in Persian Gulf Air War, November 17, [?] (Box 6, Folder 299)
  - Recent Press Clips (November 20, 1992-February 2, 1993), February 17, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 300)
    Producer: Middle East Watch, (various publications)
  - Reuters' Gaza Correspondent Enter Fifth Week in Investigative Detention: Case Belies Israel's Claim Palestinian Journalists Arrested Only for Underground Activities, February 27, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 301)
  - Situation in the West Bank and the Gaza Strip: Prepared Testimony of Kenneth Roth, Deputy Director of Human Rights Watch, May 9, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 302)
    Producer: Middle East Watch, Kenneth Roth, Human Rights Watch
  - Behind Closed Doors: Torture and Detention in Egypt, July, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 302A)
  - Under the Toughest Curfew Since 1973, West Bank and Gaza Palestinians Face Growing Hardship: Most Palestinians Still Unprotected from Iraqi Missile Attack, Despite Israeli Court Ruling, January 27, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 302B)
  - Middle East Watch Urges All Parties to Obey Rules of War Protecting Citizens: Condemns Iraq's Missile Attacks on Civilians in Israel, January 18, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 302C)
  - A day of Anti-Israel Indoctrination (conference materials), November 16, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 303)
    Producer: MOSAIC
  - Middle East Water: Critical Resource, May, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 304)
    Producer: National Geographic
  - Israeli Organizations Awarded Grants by New Israel Fund in June 1986 (typescript, 4 leaves), June, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 305)
    Producer: New Israel Fund
  - NIF Report, Spring 1992 (Box 6, Folder 305)
  - Breaking the Silence, [?]; photocopy of article, p. 20-22 (Box 6, Folder 306)
    Producer: New Outlook
  - Breaking the Silence: Soldiers' Testimonies from Operation Cast Lead, Gaza, ,2009 (Box 6, Folder 306)
  - Jerusalem Perspectives Towards a Political Settlement, July, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 307)
    Producer: New Outlook, United States Institute of Peace
  - [Miscellaneous articles from The New York Times], April 14, 1987--January 3, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 308)
    Producer: New York Times
  - (Article): Palestinian Killed by Israeli Troops: Student is One of Four Shot in the West Bank During Protests Over Arrests, April 14, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 308)
    Producer: Thomas L. Friedman, New York Times
  - (Article): Israeli Civic Watchdog Is Suddenly a Target, August 29, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 308)
    Producer: Joel Brinkley, New york Times
  - (Article): The Rabbis' Almanack of Seventh-Year Farming, December 10, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 308)
    Producer: Clyde Haberman, New York Times
  - (Article): Iraq Accused: A Case of Genocide, January 3, 1993; photocopy, 12 leaves (Box 6, Folder 308)
    Producer: Judith Miller, New York Times
  - (Article): Israelis Call off Future Dwellings in Occupied Lands, July 24, 1992; photocopy (Box 6, Folder 308)
  - An Annotated Resource Directory of Non-governmental Organizations working on the Question of Palestine in North America, [?] (Box 6, Folder 309)
    Producer: North American Coordinating Committee for NGOs working on the Question of Palestine (NACC)
  - March 1989, February 1991 (Box 6, Folder 310)
    Producer: North American Coordinating Committee for Non-Governmental Organizations on the Question of Palestine (NACC)
    Volume/Number: ****
  - The NACC Resource Guide of NGOs on the Question of Palestine: A Directory of Nongovernmental Organizations affiliated with the United Nations Divison for Palestinian Rights, June, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 311)
    Producer: North American Coodinating Committee for NGOs on the Question of Palestine
  - Action Alert: Palestinians Under Curfew Need Food, Medicine, Support, [?] (Box 6, Folder 311 A)
  - Press Release: North American emergency observer delegation touring West Bank and Gaza Strip will hold press conference on Monday, 4 March 1991 in East Jerusalem to announce effects of unprecedentedly strict curfew conditions there, March 1, 1991; transmittal (Box 6, Folder 311 B)
  - Emergency Relief for West Bank and Gaza Palestinians, February 13 1991 (Box 6, Folder 311 B)
  - Palestine Focus, March/April 1987--November/December 1989, March 1987--December 1989 (Box 6, Folder 312)
    Producer: November 29th Committee for Palestine, Palestine Solidarity Committee
    Volume/Number: 22--23, 27, 33, 35--37
  - [Background Information], March, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 313)
    Producer: Operation California
  - Ansar Prison Camp: The Testimony of Two Palestinian Prisoners, [?]; photocopy, 16 leaves (Box 6, Folder 314)
    Producer: Palestine Human Rights Campaign, Ansar Resource Center
  - Palestine Human Rights Newsletter, July/August 1988--April 1989 (Box 6, Folder 315)
    Producer: Palestine Human Rights Campaign
    Volume/Number: 8.1, 8.4, 9.1--9.2
  - The Above-Mentioned (Person) Was Identified as a Stone Thrower, December 19, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 316)
    Producer: Palestine Human Rights Information Center, Yizhar Be'er (author), Israel Shahak (translator)
  - Action Alert! "Your Land or Prison", [1991?] (Box 6, Folder 317)
    Producer: Palestine Human Rights Information Center, DataBase Project on Palestinian Human Rights
  - [Background Information], February, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 318)
    Producer: Palestine Human Rights Information Center (PHRIC)
  - (Background Information Letter), February, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 318)
  - (Background Informational Pamphlet), [?] (Box 6, Folder 318)
  - The Cost of Freedom: Palestinian Human Rights under Israeli Occupation, 1988--1990 (Box 6, Folder 319)
  - (The Cost of Freedom: Palestinian Human Rights under Israeli Occupation): 1988: A Special Report, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 319)
    Producer: Palestine Human Rights Information Center (PHRIC), DataBase Project on Palestinian Human Rights
  - (The Cost of Freedom: Palestinian Human Rights under Israeli Occupation): Annual Report: 1989, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 319)
  - (The Cost of Freedom: Palestinian Human Rights under Israeli Occupation): Annual Report: 1990, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 319)
  - Does Israel Have Death Squads?: PHRIC Study of Undercover Killings in 1991 Reveals Israel's Shoot-to-Kill Policy, [1992?] (Box 6, Folder 320)
  - Excerpted from the case file of a 12 year-old Palestinian boy from Jerusalem's Old City, [1991]; photocopy, 7 leaves (Box 6, Folder 321)
  - Fact Sheet: Palestinian Prisoners in Israeli Detention Facilities, October 1, 1992; photocopy, 1 page (Box 6, Folder 322)
  - For Immediate Release, December 30, 1990--September 29, 1992; press release (Box 6, Folder 323)
  - (For Immediate Release): PHRIC Protests Army Policy of Extra-Judicial Executions and Excessive Use of Force, December 30, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 323)
  - (For Immediate Release): Expulsion Policy Reactivated: Four Gazans Expelled, January 8, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 323)
  - (For Immediate Release): PHRIC Documentation on Palestinians Executed by Israeli Undercover Units, June 26, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 323)
  - (For Immediate Release): PHRIC Protests Death of Detainee During Interrogation; Demands Independent Investigation, Access to Detainees by Lawyers and Medical Doctors, February 5, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 323)
  - (For Immediate Release): PHRIC and PCATI Demand International Investigation of Israeli Torture Unit; Express Concern Regarding Safety of Torture Victims, March 3, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 323)
    Producer: Palestine Human Rights Information Center (PHRIC), Public Committee Against Torture in Israel
  - (For Immediate Release): Israeli Authorities Issue Restrictions Against PHRIC Human Rights Worker Who Helped Expose Police Torture Unit; Obstruct Investigation into Unit, March 4, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 323)
  - (For Immediate Release): Israeli Military Authorities Ban Travel to Jerusalem and Israel for PHRIC Author of Report on Electric Shock Torture, March 17, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 323)
  - (For Immediate Release): Special Israeli Army Units and Security Forces Step Up Killing of Palestinian Activists, March 26, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 323)
  - (For Immediate Release): Palestinian Prisoners Begin Open Hunger Strike to Protest Deteriorating Conditions and Treatment, September 29, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 323)
  - From the Field, September 1990--January 1994 (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - (From the Field): Excessive Force and Collective Punishment in Breij Refugee Camp, September, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - (From the Field): Prolonged Curfew on the Palestinian Population, February, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - (From the Field): The Arrest, Detention and Physical Abuse of Palestinian Children, August/September 1991 (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - (From the Field): Detention and Interrogation of Palestinian Detainees: Torture, Deaths in Detention and Prison Conditions: February 1992, February, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - (From the Field): A Labor Force Under 'Security' Control: New Israeli Measures Restricting Palestinian Workers, July/August 1992 (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - (From the Field): Settlement Freeze-What Does it Really Mean?, September/October 1992 (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - (From the Field): Palestinian Prisoners Hold 19-Day Hunger Strike to Protest Deteriorating Conditions and Treatment, November, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - (From the Field): Transfer! Illegal Expulsion Policy Reactivated: Israel Orders Mass Deportations of Palestinians from Occupied Territories, December 1992/January 1993 (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - (From the Field):, March/April 1993; incomplete, p. 3-18 (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - (From the Field): Israeli Closure Forces Nine Jerusalem Villages Under Virtual House Arrest, May, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - (From the Field): While Soldiers Watched-Settlers Rampage in Hebron During 7-Day Curfew; Residents Evicted; Houses Burned, June, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - (From the Field): Street Hawkers or Unemployed: The Economic Impact of the 'Closure', August, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - (From the Field): A Bittersweet Coming Home: The Experience of Palestinians Returning from the Gulf, October, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - (From the Field): Settler Lawlessness in the Occupied Territories: Deliberate Shootings, Racist Attacks and Mob Violence, November/December 1993 (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - (From the Field): Whose Jerusalem? Continuing Israeli Annexation of Occupied East Jerusalem After the Oslo Agreements, January, 1994; photocopy, 6 pages (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - Human Rights Issues Post-Madrid, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 325)
  - Human Rights Update, January 1990, March--May 1990 (Box 6, Folder 326)
    Producer: Palestine Human Rights Information Center (PHRIC), Database Project on Palestinian Human Rights, Arab Studies Society
    Volume/Number: 3.2, 3.4--3.6
  - Human Rights Update, June 1990--October 1990 (Box 6, Folder 327)
    Volume/Number: 3.7--3.11
  - Human Rights Update, November 1990--January-February 1991, May 1991--June 1991, November 1990--June 1991 (Box 7, Folder 328)
    Volume/Number: 3.12--4.2, 4.5--4.6
  - Human Rights Violations Summary Data, 1990--1992 (Box 7, Folder 329)
  - (Human Rights Violations Summary Data): Uprising, Years 1, 2, and 3: December 8, 1987 through December 8, 1990, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 329)
  - (Human Rights Violations Summary Data): By Month, 1991, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 329)
  - (Human Rights Violations Summary Data): From December 9, 1987 through June 30, 1992, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 329)
  - Information Bulletin: Israel Orders 12 Palestinians Expelled from Occupied Territories, January, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 330)
  - The Massacre of Palestinians at Al-Haram Al Sharif, October 8, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 331)
  - Memorandum: Emergency Situation of Palestinian Prisoners' Hunger Strike, October 10, 1992; photocopy, 1 page (Box 7, Folder 332)
    Producer: Palestine Human Rights Information Center (PHRIC), Al-Haq, Mandela Institute
  - Nonviolence and Death at Bir Zeit University: An Investigative Report, June, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 333)
    Producer: Palestine Human Rights Information Center (PHRIC), HRREF/DataBase Project, Frank Collins, Ph.D.
  - Palestinian Deaths Due to Torture in Interrogation, December 8, 1987--April 30, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 334)
  - Palestinian Prisoners Hunger Strike into its 13th Day; Human Rights Groups Concerned about Prisoners' Health, October 9, 1992; photocopy, 1 page (Box 7, Folder 335)
  - Palestinian Prisoners' Strike Demands, November, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 336)
  - Palestinians Killed by Israeli Occupation Forces, Settlers, Civilians and Collaborators During the Second Year of the Uprising: December 9, 1988 through December 8, 1989, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 337)
  - Palestinians Killed by Israeli Security Forces at the Haram al-Sharif, October 8, 1990, October 18, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 338)
  - Palestinians Under Administrative Detention: Confirmed Cases, January 5-February 15, 1988; transmission, 2 leaves (Box 7, Folder 339)
  - Pathways to Peace (Background Information and Letter of Transmittal), 1992 (Box 7, Folder 340)
  - PHRIC Expresses Concert About Expansion of Israeli Settlements in the Occupied Territories, March 10, 1991; transmission, 2 leaves (Box 7, Folder 341)
  - Publications of the Palestine Human Rights Information Center, [1991?] (Box 7, Folder 342)
  - Targeting to Kill: Israel's Undercover Units, May, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 343)
    Producer: Palestine Human Rights Information Center (PHRIC), Center for Policy Analysis on Palestine
  - Torture Unit (Unofficial/Rough Translation), February 24, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 344)
    Producer: Palestine Human Rights Information Center (PHRIC) (translator), Doron Me'iri (original author), Hadashot
  - The Massacre of Palestinians at Al-Haram Al-Sharif: A Special Investigative Report, October 8, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 344 A)
  - The Massacre in Al-Haram Al-Ibrahimi Al-Sharif: Context and Aftermath, May, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 344 A)
  - 1998 Annual Report Narrative and Financial Reports, January 1--December 31, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 345)
    Producer: Palestinian Centre for Human Rights
  - The Voice of the Voiceless, July, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 346)
    Producer: Palestinian Centre for Rapprochement Between People, Gh. Andoni (editor)
  - Women's Human Rights Project: Background Paper, October 10, 1991--April 22, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 347)
    Producer: Palestinian Federation of Women's Action Committees, Beth Goldring
  - (Women's Human Rights Project: Background Paper): Problems in Palestinian Residence Following the Gulf War, October 10, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 347)
  - (Women's Human Rights Project: Background Paper): Developments in Emergency Palestinian Residence Issues, April 22, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 347)
  - A Jewish Refuatation of "Israel", December, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 348)
    Producer: Palestinian Jewish Neturei Karta Organization
  - Cooperating against Justice: Human Rights Violations by Israel and the Palestinian National Authority following the Murders in Wadi Qelt, July, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 349)
    Producer: Palestinian Society for the Protection of Human Rights and the Environment, B'Tselem
  - Freedom-to-Write Bulletin, January/February 1992 (Box 7, Folder 350)
    Producer: PEN American Center
  - A Newsletter to Our Friends in North America, Summer 1988 (Box 7, Folder 351)
    Producer: Peace Now
    Volume/Number: 4.1
  - Israel's Settlement Activities, January 22, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 352)
    Producer: Peace Now, Settlements Watch Committee
  - The Casualties of Conflict: Medical Care and Human Rights in the West Bank and Gaza Strip: Report of a Medical Fact Finding Mission by Physicians for Human Rights, March 30, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 353)
    Producer: Physicians for Human Rights
  - Harm to Medical Personnel: The Delay, Abuse and Humiliation of Medical Personnel by Israeli Security Forces, December, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 354)
    Producer: Physicians for Human Rights, B'Tselem
  - Health Care in Detention: A Study of Israel's Treatment of Palestinians, April, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 355)
  - Human Rights on Hold: A Report on Emergency Measures and Access to Health Care in the Occupied Territories: 1990-1992, June, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 355A)
  - Annual Activity Report, 1989, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 356)
    Producer: Popular Committees for Heath Services (PCHS)
  - [Information and data regarding the Popular Committees for Health Services], [?]; photocopy, 11 leaves (Box 7, Folder 357)
  - Newsletter, [1989] (Box 7, Folder 358)
  - Proposal for Possible Support, April 11, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 359)
  - About the B'Tselem Report, [1991?] (Box 7, Folder 360)
    Producer: Public Committee Against Torture in Israel (PCATI)
  - Failure to Investigate the Alleged Torture of Lamia Ismail Jaber i.d. #990270357: A Call for Action, September, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 361)
  - The High Court of Justice on G.S.S. Interrogations, April 16, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 362)
    Producer: Public Committee Against Torture in Israel (PCATI), Ha'aretz
  - Position Paper, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 363)
    Producer: Public Committee Against Torture in Israel (PCATI), Hannah Friedman
  - To the members of the Knesset and the government of Israel: Demands, [?] (Box 7, Folder 364)
  - Moderate Physical Pressure: Interrogation Methods in Israel, December 7 1990 (Box 7, Folder 364)
  - [Legal briefs and associated documents, Everett Mendelson…[et al.], plantiffs, against Edwin M. Meese, III [US Attorny General], defendant], March, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 365)
    Producer: Rabinowitz, Boudin, Standard, Krinksky & Lieberman, P.C.
  - Update on the Situation of School Education in the Occupied Palestinian Territories, February 28, 1991; transmission, 1 page (Box 7, Folder 366)
    Producer: Ramallah Friends Schools
  - Ramya-The Struggle to Stay on the Land: Background and Update June 1992, June, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 367)
    Producer: Ramya Solidarity Committee, Rabbis for Human Rights
  - Yes on W: Palestinian Israeli Peace, [1988?] (Box 7, Folder 368)
    Producer: San Franciscans for Palestinian Israeli Peace
  - Sanabel Briefing Paper: Mass Expulsions of 'Non-Residents' Become Routinized, September 4, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 369)
    Producer: Sanabel Press Services
  - Transfer Policy in Action: The Expulsion of Non-Residents, December 31, 1989; photocopy, 18 leaves (Box 7, Folder 370)
  - Bulletin of Regional Cooperation in the Middle East, March 1, 1992--Winter 1995/96 (Box 7, Folder 371)
    Producer: Search for Common Ground (SCG), Initiative for Peace and Cooperation in the Middle East (IPCME)
    Volume/Number: 1.1--1.2, 2.3--3.1, 4.4
  - (Included): Profiles of Organizations, [?] (Box 7, Folder 371)
    Producer: Search for Common Ground (SCG)
  - Comments About the Work of SEARCH, [1991?] (Box 7, Folder 372)
    Producer: Search for Justice and Equality in Palestine
  - Palestine/Israel Bulletin, April, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 373)
  - Recent Human Rights Reports Critical of Israel, August, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 374)
  - Briefing Paper, January 1992--[?] 1992 (Box 7, Folder 375)
    Producer: Settlement Watch
  - (Briefing Paper): Soviet Jews: Whose Humanitarian Concern?, January, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 375)
  - (Briefing Paper): Israeli Settlements: Against the Law, [?] 1992 (Box 7, Folder 375)
  - [Background Information], December 6, 1991; transmission, 3 leaves (Box 7, Folder 376)
    Producer: Society of St. Ives
  - [Petition against the "prolonged curfews"], February 28, 1991; transmission, 1 page (Box 7, Folder 377)
  - St. Yves Legal Newsletter, December 1, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 378)
    Producer: Society of St. Yves
  - The Status of Palestinian Children during the Uprising in the Occupied Territories: Child Death and Injury: A Chronology, January, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 379)
    Producer: Swedish Save the Children, Anne Elizabeth Nixon
  - The Status of Palestinian Children during the Uprising in the Occupied Territories: Child Death and Injury: Appendices, January, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 380)
  - The Status of Palestinian Children during the Uprising in the Occupied Territories: Collective Punishment, January, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 381)
  - Urgent Issues Regarding The Forcible Separation of Palestinian Families, September 14, 1992; Typescript (Box 7, Folder 381a)
    Producer: Convention on the Rights of the Child, United Nations
  - Note Regarding the Registration of Palestinian Children, October 23, 1992; Typescript (Box 7, Folder 381a)
  - Problems in Palestinan Family Reunification, November 5, 1992; typescript (Box 7, Folder 381a)
  - Families Torn Apart: Separation of Palestinian Families in the Occupied Territories, July, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 381a)
    Producer: Center for the Defence of the Individual
  - Agreement on Prepatory Transfer of Powers and Responsibilities, August 29, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 382)
    Producer: State of Israel,
  - The Middle East Peace Process, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 383)
    Producer: State of Israel
  - Murder and Hypocrisy in Israel, October 24, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 384)
    Producer: The Struggle, Stanley Heller (editor), Middle East Crisis Committee
    Volume/Number: 54
  - Third World Resources: A Quarterly Review of Resources From and About the Third World, January/March 1990--October/December 1992, January 1990--December 1992 (Box 7, Folder 385)
    Producer: Third World Resources, DataCenter
    Volume/Number: 7.1--8.4
  - Third World Resources: A Quarterly Review of Resources From and About the Third World, July/September 1993--April/June 1994 (Box 7, Folder 386)
    Volume/Number: 9.3--10.2
  - Healing the Wounds of Occupation, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 387)
    Producer: Union of Health Work Committees
  - Objectives, Organization, and Activities, [1990] (Box 7, Folder 388)
    Producer: Union of Palestinian Medical Relief Committees
  - Bulletin, December 1987--February 1991 (Box 7, Folder 389)
    Producer: United Nations, Division for Palestinian Rights
    Volume/Number: 10.12--11.1, 13.4, 13.8, 13.10--14.2
  - Eigth United Nations Seminar on the Question of Palestine, June 22-23, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 390)
    Producer: United Nations
  - (Eigth United Nations Seminar on the Question of Palestine): Theme: Enforcing the Fourth Geneva Convention for ensuring the protectino of the Palestinian people in the occupied Palestinian Territory, June 22-23, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 390)
    Producer: Jeanne Butterfield
  - (Eigth United Nations Seminar on the Question of Palestine): Provisional List of Participants, June 22-23, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 390)
  - Ninth United Nations North American NGO Symposium on the Question of Palestine [papers], June 24-26, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 391)
    Producer: United Nations, North American Coordinating Committee for NGOs on the Question of Palestine (NACC), Division for Palestinian Rights
  - (Ninth United Nations North American NGO Symposium on the Question of Palestine): Opening Statement, June 24-26, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 391)
    Producer: Victor Camilleri
  - (Ninth United Nations North American NGO Symposium on the Question of Palestine): Opening Session: Statement, June 24-26, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 391)
  - (Ninth United Nations North American NGO Symposium on the Question of Palestine): 25 Years of Occupation: Overcoming the Obstacles: The Peace Process, June 24-26, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 391)
    Producer: Dr. Haidar Abdel Shafi
  - (Ninth United Nations North American NGO Symposium on the Question of Palestine): Occupation Update: The Human Rights Situation in the Occupied Territories, June 24-26, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 391)
    Producer: Raji Sourani
  - (Ninth United Nations North American NGO Symposium on the Question of Palestine): Israeli Settlements, June 24-26, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 391)
  - (Ninth United Nations North American NGO Symposium on the Question of Palestine): Needs of Palestinians in Hardship Areas, June 24-26, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 391)
    Producer: Elia Zureik